(Penny:)Raj, honey...
(Penny:)...you say you can't talk to women
but you've been talking to me.
(Sheldon:)And now we'll never know.
(Raj:)You're right. I...
(Raj:)I am talking to you.
(Raj:)Hello, Penny. How are you?
(Penny:)I'm fine.
Okay, now, I need to
make sure I have a Lalita...
(Raj:)...before I meet the Grasshopper.
(Raj:)It's a sweet green miracle.
If you're gonna drink on this date,
just promise me you won't overdo it.
(Raj:)Overdo what?
(Raj:)Happiness?
(Raj:)Freedom?
(Raj:)This warm glow inside of me that promises
everything's going to be all hunky dunky?
(Penny:)Yeah, that.
(Penny:)Why don't you bring her to my restaurant
so I can keep an eye on you?
(Leonard:)Okay.
What's the plan? Let's say he meets her,
he likes her, they get married.
What's he gonna do,
stay drunk for the rest of his life?